Guide to the Records of the Office of the Chancellor (Elmer Ellsworth Brown) RG.3.0.4
New York University Archives
- Series I: Administrative Files
  - Strauss, Manny (President, Bankers Industrial Corporation), 1924-1932 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Student Army Training Corps, 1918-1919 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Student Dramatics, NYU, 1912-1929 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Student Organizations, 1911-1932, undated (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Students Protective Association, 1932 (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Student Senate, 1924, 1933 (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - Student Straw Ballot, Presidential Election, 1912 (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - Stunkard, Dr. Horace W. (Professor of Biology), 1923-1930 (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - Suhrie, Ambrose L. (Professor, Teacher's College), 1925-1933, undated (Box 67, Folder 15)
  - Sulgrave Institution, 1920-1926, undated (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Summer School: Pamphlets and Circulars, 1919, 1922-1926, undated (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Summer School: Proposed Changes, 1929 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Sussman, Samuel, Memorial Prize, 1920-1924 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Syracuse University, 1924-1932 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Taft, Henry, 1920-1927, 1930, undated (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Tamblyn and Brown, 1920, 1922-1923, 1926 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Tanner, Rollin M. (Professor of Classics), 1924-1931 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Taxation and Education Institutions, 1916-1918 (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Taylor, A. Wellington (Dean, Graduate School of Business Administration), 1918, 1920-1933 (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - Taylor, Mrs. Frederick: Library, 1920, 1922 (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - Taylor, Myron, 1928, 1930-1931, undated (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - Teneyck, Andrew (Director of Publicity), 1919-1921, 1924, 1926 (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - Thayer, Mrs. John Van Buren, 1924, 1927 (Box 68, Folder 14)
  - Thompson, Frederick Ferris, 1922 (Box 68, Folder 15)
  - Thompson, Dr. Annis E. (Secretary, Treasurer, Park Portrait Fund), 1927-1928 (Box 68, Folder 16)
  - Thorne, Perley L. (Assistant Dean, University College of Arts and Pure Science), 1919-1932, undated (Box 68, Folder 17)
  - Thrasher, Professor Frederic M. (Director, Boy's Club Study), 1928-1932 (Box 68, Folder 18)
  - Thrasher, Professor Frederic M. (Director, Boy's Club Study): Preliminary Report of Boy's Club Study, 1929 (Box 68, Folder 19)
  - "Thursday Morning Talks" Notes, 1917, undated (Box 68, Folder 20)
  - Thwing, Charles F. (President, Western Reserve University), 1921-1923, 1925-1926 (Box 68, Folder 21)
  - Tiffany and Company, 1921, 1923-1924 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Tilton, Edgar S. (Assistant Secretary, University and Bellevue Hospital Medical College, 1918-1933 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Tompkins, Leslie J. (Attorney at Law), 1918-1931 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Tonsor, Charles A. (Professor of English), 1919-1929 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Tooke, Charles W. (Professor of Law), 1925, 1928-1932 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Torrey, Harry Beal, 1925, 1927, 1929 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Town Hall Club (Town Hall), 1923-1932 (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Turner, John R. (Dean, Washington Square College), 1917, 1919-1924 (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Turner, John R. (Dean, Washington Square College), 1925-1931 (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Tuskegee Normal and Instructional Institute, 1921-1932 (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - Tyler, Hazen G. (Professor of Mechanical Engineering), 1920-1926, undated (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - Underwood, Horace Grant (Chosen Christian College, Seoul, Korea), 1915-1919 (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - Underwood, Dr. Horace G. (Chairman of Cooperating Board of Christian Education in Chosen College, NYC), 1922-1932, undated (Box 69, Folder 13)
  - Underwood, John T. (Underwood Typewriter Company), 1921-1926 (Box 69, Folder 14)
  - Unemployment Relief Committee, 1930-1933 (Box 69, Folder 15)
  - Union Theological Seminary, 1919-1933, undated (Box 69, Folder 16)
  - United Parents Associations, 1927-1929 (Box 69, Folder 17)
  - United States Senate, 1919 (Box 69, Folder 18)
  - United States Civil Service, 1919-1924 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - United States Bureau of Education (Department of Interior), 1913-1919 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - United States House of Representatives: Congressman Fees' Bill re National University, undated (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - United States Naval Academy, 1918, 1920, 1925-1929, undated (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - University Attorney, Office of, 1928-1935 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - University Club of New York, 1924-1926, 1928-1932 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - University Day, 1913-1916 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - University, and Federal Law, 1917-1918 (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - University Heights: Buildings, 1913-1918, 1920, undated (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - University Heights: Dumps, 1916-1917 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - University Heights: Property, 1910, 1912-1916 (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - University Heights: Proposed Incinerator, 1925-1926 (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - University of the State of New York, 1918-1933 (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - University Representation, 1912-1923 (Box 70, Folder 14)
  - University Representatives at Conferences, 1919-1922 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Vacancies, Committee on, 1918 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Van Demark, R. W.: Samuel Colcord and Nobel Prize, 1928-1929 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Van Etten, Dr. Nathan B. (Chairman, Committee on Nurses and Nursing Education, American Medical Association), 1919-1933 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Van Glabbeke, Adolphe, 1928-1929 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Van Roosbrooeck, Dr. G. L., 1924, 1927-1932 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Vanamee, Mrs. Grace D. (Acting Director, Hall of Fame), 1920-1922 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Veterans of Foreign Wars, 1919, 1928, 1931 (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Veterinary College, 1910-1922 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Victory Hall, 1920-1921 (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - Vigneron, Marcel (Professor of French), 1929, 1931 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Violet Bonds, 1924, 1926-1927 (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - Vir Publishing Company, 1919-1920 (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - Volunteers of America, 1929 (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - Von Der Osten, Hans, 1926-1929 (Box 71, Folder 15)
  - Von Klenze, Camillo, 1926 (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - Voorhis, Harold O. (V.P. and Secretary), 1922-1934 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Wadley and Smythe, Florists, 1925-1930, 1932 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - The Waldorf-Astoria, 1923, 1931 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Walker, F. A. ("Al"), 1924-1933 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Walker, Ralph C. (Concert Chairman, University Heights), 1920-1922 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - War Barracks, 1915, 1918-1919 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - War Emergency Committee, 1917 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Warburg, Paul M., 1919-1932 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Ward, John Quincy Adams Memorial Collection, 1922-1923, 1925 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Washburn, Earle L. (Auditor), 1919, 1924-1933 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Washington (George) Bicentennial Celebration Chancellor's Committee, 1931-1932 (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Washington Square, 1926 (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - Washington Square Association, 1924-1927 (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - Washington Square Building (Main Building), 1914-1925, undated (Box 72, Folder 14)
  - Washington Square College, 1926-1932 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Washington Square College Association, 1919 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Washington Square College Deans Conference, 1924 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Washington Square College Deanship: Faculty Suggestions of Candidates to Succeed Dean Munn, 1932 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Washington Square Collegiate Division, 1912-1913 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Washington Square Dealer, 1918-1920 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Washington Square Players, 1921-1929 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Waters, William E. (Professor of Greek), 1918-1925 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Watson, Katherine, 1932 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Watt, Homer A. (Associate Professor of English), 1919-1928, 1930-1932 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Webb, Edwin D. (Secretary of Law School), 1922-1931 (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Weeks, John W. (U.S. Secretary of War), 1921-1922, 1925-1926 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Wellesley College, 1916-1932 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Welling, Richard (Chairman, Self-Government, Inc.), 1923-1932 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Wellman, Walter, 1919 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Wendel, Professor Hugo C. M. (New York University Choir Society), 1921-1926 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Wesleyan University, 1917, 1925-1926, 1931-1932, undated (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Whipple, Leonidas (Professor of Journalism), 1921-1924 (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Whistler, James McNeill: Bronze Bust, 1928 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - White, Richard Grant (Father of Stanford White; Architect), 1925 (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - White, Stanford: Ceremony, 1921 (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - White Supremacy League, 1923-1924 (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - White, Theodore G., Fund (Government House), 1912-1916, 1919 (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - Whitehouse, J. Howard: English Education Exhibit, 1926-1928 (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - Whitman, Dr. Frank S. (President, The People's Bank of Belvedere, Illinois), 1931-1932 (Box 74, Folder 14)
  - Who's Who in America, 1917-1933 (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - Wiener, William (Principal, Central High School, Newark, NJ), 1919 (Box 74, Folder 16)
  - Wightman, Dr. Percy B., 1920-1921, 1926, 1932 (Box 74, Folder 17)
  - Wiley, Louis (New York Times), 1922, 1929-1932, undated (Box 74, Folder 18)
  - Wilkens, Frederick F., 1921-1932 (Box 74, Folder 19)
  - Wiship, Albert E. (Editor, Journal of Education), 1920-1924, 1930-1931 (Box 74, Folder 20)
  - Withers, John W. (Dean, School of Education), 1919-1920 (Box 74, Folder 21)
  - Withers, John W., 1921-1922 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Withers, John W., 1923-1924 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Withers, John W., 1925-1926 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Withers, John W., 1927-1928 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Withers, John W., 1929-1930 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Withers, John W., 1931-1933 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Woman's Law Class, 1910, 1917-1924, undated (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Woodman, Dr. Joseph Edmund (Professor of Geology), 1919-1933 (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Workers Education Bureau, 1922 (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - World Alliance For International Friendship (Through the Churches), 1922-1933 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - World Conference on Narcotic Education, 1926, 1928 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - World's Court League, Inc., 1917 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - World War I Activities, 1918 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - World War I Activities, 1918 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - World War I Activities, 1914-1917 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - World War I Activities, 1918 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - World War I Activities, 1919-1925, 1928-1930 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - World War I: Correspondence, 1917-1919 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Wright, Orville, 1925, 1927 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Wright, Mr. And Mrs. Orville Ross (no relation to Inventor), 1917-1919 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Wyckoff, John H. (Dean, University and Bellevue Hospital Medical College), 1919-1933 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Yale University, 1918-1933, undated (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Young Men's Christian Association, 1923-1927 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Young Men's Christian Association, 1928-1929 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Young Men's Christian Association, 1930-1931 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Young Men's Christian Association, 1932-1933 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Young Men's Christian Association: International Committee, 1913-1916 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Young Women's Christian Association, 1926, 1929-1931 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Young, Owen D., 1927-1928, 1930-1932 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Zabriskie, George, 1920-1921, 1924, 1931-1932 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Zimmerman, Dr. Erich W., 1918, undated (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Zinnecker, Dr. Wesley D. (Professor of German), 1920-1932 (Box 78, Folder 8)
- Series II: Miscellaneous Correspondence
  This series is alphabetically arranged.
  - Aa-Al, 1915-1932, undated (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Am-Aq, 1914-1931, undated (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Ar-Az, 1914-1933 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Ba-Bd, 1915-1932 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Be-Bh, 1915-1933 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Bi-Bn, 1913-1932 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Bo-Bq, 1912-1933, undated (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Bra-Bri, 1915-1932 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - Brj-Bt, 1912-1934 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - Bu-Bz, 1913-1925, undated (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - Ca-Cd, 1914-1932 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Ce-Ch, 1912-1932 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Ci-Cn, 1913-1933 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Coa-Col, 1913-1923 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Com-Cq, 1912-1931, undated (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Cr-Cz, 1915-1932 (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - Da-De, 1915-1935 (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - Df-Dz, 1912-1933, undated (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - E, 1906-1934, undated (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - Fa-Fz, 1914-1934 (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - Ga-Gh, 1920-1934 (Box 80, Folder 11)
  - Gi-Gz, 1915-1935 (Box 80, Folder 12)
  - Ha-Hd, 1920-1934 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - He-Hh, 1919-1933, undated (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Hi-Hn, 1910-1932 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Hoa-Hol, 1916-1934 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Hom-Hor, 1916-1933 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Hos-Hoz, 1912-1934, undated (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Hp-Hz, 1920-1933, undated (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Ia-In, 1920-1933, undated (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - Io-Iz, 1920-1935, undated (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - Ja-Jd, 1915-1933, undated (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Je-Jn, 1913-1933 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Jo-Jz, 1916-1934 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Ka-Kd, 1919-1933 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Ke-Kem, 1917-1932 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Ken-Kez, 1920-1935 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Kf-Kk, 1916-1933, undated (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Kl-Kq, 1912-1933, undated (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - Kr-Kz, 1919-1933 (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - La-Lal, 1917-1932 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Lam-Laq, 1920-1933, undated (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Lar-Laz, 1919-1933 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Lea-Lel, 1920-1935, undated (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Len-Lez, 1919-1933, undated (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Lf-Lim, 1920-1933, undated (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Lin-Liz, 1919-1932, undated (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - Lj-Lt, 1919-1933, undated (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Lu-Lz, 1912-1933, undated (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - McA-McC, 1919-1932, undated (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - McD-McG, 1919-1934 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - McH-McZ, 1921-1933, undated (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - Maa-Mag, 1919-1931, undated (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - Mah-Man, 1917-1932, undated (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - Mao-Mar, 1917-1934 (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Mas-Maz, 1919-1933 (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - Mb-Mer, 1919-1933, undated (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Mes-Mez, 1919-1933, undated (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Mf-Mij, 1919-1930 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Mik-Mim, 1919-1933, undated (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Min-Mon, 1916-1935, undated (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Moo-Moq, 1921-1935, undated (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Mor-Moz, 1914-1934 undated (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - Mp-Mz, 1916-1934, undated (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - National A-B, 1912-1933, undated (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - National C-D, 1919-1933, undated (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - National E-Z, 1919-1933 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - Na-Nd, 1920-1930 (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - Nea-Nev, 1918-1933 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - New A-T, 1919-1934 (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - New U-Z - Nez, 1918-1934 (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - Nf-Nn, 1920-1934 (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - No-Nz, 1920-1933, undated (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Oa-Oh, 1919-1934, undated (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - Oi-Orx, 1919-1934 (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - O'ry-Oz, 1919-1933, undated (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Pac-Pap, 1913-1933, undated (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - Paq-Par, 1922-1932, undated (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - Pas-Paz, 1919-1934, undated (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - Pb-Peq, 1919-1933, undated (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - Per-Pf, 1917-1934, undated (Box 87, Folder 9)
  - Pg-Ph, 1911-1933, undated (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Pi-Pj, 1919-1933, undated (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - Pk-Pl, 1922-1931 (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Po-Pq, 1921-1933, undated (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - Pr, 1911-1933, undated (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - Ps-Pz, 1918-1933, undated (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - Qa-Qz, 1921-1932, undated (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - Ra-Rb, 1919-1933, undated (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Rc-Re, 1914-1934, undated (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Rf-Rn, 1915-1934, undated (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - Roa-Rol, 1918-1933, undated (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Rom-Roz, 1919-1935, undated (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Rp-Rz, 1920-1933, undated (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - Saa-Saq, 1919-1935, undated (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - Sar-Sd, 1913-1934, undated (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - Se-Sg, 1920-1934, undated (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Sha-Shh, 1920-1935, undated (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - Shi-Shz, 1920-1933 (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - Si--Sj, 1920-1935 (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - Sk-Smn, 1918-1934, undated (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - Smo-So, 1919-1933, undated (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Sp-Ss, 1918-1933, undated (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - Sta-Sth, 1914-1934, undated (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - Sti-Stq, 1921-1932, undated (Box 90, Folder 9)
  - Str-Stt, 1920-1932, undated (Box 90, Folder 10)
  - Stu-Stz, 1921-1933, undated (Box 90, Folder 11)
  - Su, 1920-1933, undated (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Sv-Sz, 1911-1933 (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Ta-Td, 1919-1933 (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Te-Thn, 1923-1933, undated (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - Tho-Thq, 1919-1933 (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - Thr-To, 1920-1932, undated (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - Tp-Ts, 1919-1933 (Box 91, Folder 7)
  - Tt-Tz, 1920-1932, undated (Box 91, Folder 8)
  - U, 1890-1933, undated (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - United States, 1919-1933 (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - University, 1919-1933 (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Va-Vh, 1919-1933 (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Vi-Vz, 1919-1939, undated (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - Wa-Wal, 1919-1933, undated (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - Wam-Waz, 1918-1933, undated (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - Wb-Wel, 1920-1933 (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - Wem-Whh, 1920-1933, undated (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Whi-Whz, 1919-1933, undated (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - Wi-Wim, 1913-1933, undated (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Win-Wn, 1920-1933 (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - Woe-Won, 1914-1933, undated (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - Woo-Woq, 1919-1932, undated (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - Wor-Wos, 1920-1931 (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - Wot-Wz, 1919-1932, undated (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - X-Y, 1918-1933, undated (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - Z, 1919-1933, undated (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - RESTRICTED MATERIAL (Box 106)
- Addresses and Published Articles
  - Addresses and Published Articles, 1890-1908 (Box 95)
  - Addresses and Published Articles, 1910-1917 (Box 96)
  - Addresses and Published Articles, 1918-1922 (Box 97)
  - Addresses and Published Articles, 1923-1927 (Box 98)
  - Addresses and Published Articles (Box 99)
  - Addresses and Published Articles, 1931-1934 (Box 100)
  - "The Making of Our Middle Schools," Addresses and Published Writings, Speeches, Clippings Citations, 1914-1933 (Box 101)
  - "The Making of Our Middle Schools" (Box 102)
  - "The Making of our Middle Schools," "A Few Remarks", 1919-1934 (Box 103)
  - Verse, 1884-1932 (Box 104)